My name is Akari Umura from Juice=Juice.
I will be your MC for the next two sessions.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
I am 15 years old, a first-year high school student, and my name is Yanagisawa, born on December 30.
My favorite foods are strawberries and chocolate,
I dislike eggplant and melon.
And today, I have done a haircut that I have done in the hair arrangement section.
I'm getting used to it, so I've been wearing this hairstyle at handshakes and other events.
Hello! This time, my partners are Akari Uemura of Juice Juice and Ruru Danbara of Juice Juice.
and Ruru Danbara from Juice Juice.
This time, I'll be talking with Akari Uemura of Juice Juice and Ruru Danbara of Juice Juice.
This is Akari Uemura's last show before her graduation. As this is my last MC for Halo!
I started with the video of my first MC.
I saw it at the meeting today, so I'd like to share it with you.
I saw it at the meeting, so I was looking for the same hair style.
I was looking for a hair elastic.
I asked the staff if they had a hair elastic, and I borrowed it.
When I look at the old video like this...
I can see what you cherished back then.
I was able to see them before I graduated.
I think it's a very good memory.
I have more hairstyles that I'm thinking of doing again.
But it's so cute, and it hasn't changed much.
Lulu tells me this every time.
When I do my stage makeup, I put on a lot of eye makeup.
But if I didn't wear eye makeup, I'd look like the old Uemura-san.
But if I didn't wear eye makeup, I wouldn't be able to match the side of my eyes with Mr. Kamimura's now.
I can match with the current Uemura-san, so much so that I don't feel uncomfortable even if I stand next to him.
But the way he speaks, he still sounds like the Uemura-san of 10 years ago.
I also thought that was a nice touch.
Yes, that's right.
So today, we Juice=Juice released our new singles "Naimono-Love" and "Aiko" in Tokyo Bra!
Thank you very much.
It's a triple A-side single, and the fourth track is a solo song by Ms. Uemura.
Yes, it's a coupling track.
It's called "Brilliance of Memories", and it was written by Aoi Yamazaki.
Aoi Yamazaki, director of the band, and I had not decided anything yet.
We hadn't decided on the sound or the lyrics yet, so I wanted them to get to know me first.
What I remember most from the conversation is the origin of my name.
I remember that I told him that the origin of my name is very much connected to the present.
I was so happy to have this new experience in my 11th year, so please listen to this song.
I'm sure I'll listen to it at the same time with my Juice=Juice family.
I'm sure I'll be listening to it with my Juice=Juice family.
I'm looking forward to it!
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go.
You've come to sometime, haven't you?
(Positive, negative, half negative, half positive, tomorrow's the day.)
I always want to blame others... that's all I want to do... until my hand waves
I want to forgive you, but I'll pretend I memorized it, and I want to forgive you, but you know...
You look sad and chaotic. I hate the city.
I came up the stairs and it was so bright and I was so mad at it
I'm so upset because I'm dazzled by the sparkling tomorrow.
Summer winds are wandering around
Memories are changing colors, and they're stained with regret...
It's kind of a lovely color, isn't it?
I wanna be
Departure, the road of passing
wakai eien no kouryuu kai
Still, I don't know since that day
I'll always be flooded with memories
No way, no way, no way, no way, no way
What really happened before
But that's not the truth
But the fact that I've been able to push myself...
It's calming.
But it's not.
The bright white
The twilight that piled up
Those days of greatness
than shoes similar to today
Even if I'm the one
You can't imagine
Than I could walk down the glittering road of the future
So nostalgic and tender
Memories keep coming
I'm so frustrated that I can't stand it
I can't wait to see your idols
Kira Kira
Bebe
Here we go
From a sparkling tomorrow, as if we're already running, we've landed in nostalgia
Right now, memories are layering colors, blotting them out, but they're still somehow
It's a lovely color so that I can walk down the glittering road of the future
It's nostalgic, it's gentle, and these are the memories that keep disappearing, so much so that I can't stand it.
It smells so good, it's so frustrating
Words, Music, Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Thank you for everything, I'm rooting for you too
With Akuri Uemura of Juice Juice
I'd like to tell you a little bit about each other.
I'd like to tell you a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So let's answer at a quick pace without thinking too much!
Last Tuesday, Ruru turned 23 years old.
Please make a vow at 23 years old.
I will enjoy myself to the fullest!
On the day of my birthday, I'm releasing my photo book, Ruru Ruru Ruru.
What were your honest impressions of your first photo book shoot?
The scenery of Yaku Island was very beautiful.
In reference to your new single "Tokyo Brown", what has become clear to you recently?
The intonation of bamboo shoots.
What's the point of your outfit today?
Oh, it's the jacket that Mr. Kamimura gave me!
What do you remember most in the 7 years you have been working together as Juice=Juice?
We had a lot of meals together.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Lulu.
We have been working together as Juice=Juice for about 7 years, and we have made an impact.
We are called Lulu Early.
As a sub-leader and leader, we had a lot of memories.
What was the most memorable one?
Eating a lot of food!
Let's hear it, let's hear it.
I'm sure if you dig deep enough, you'll find a lot.
That's right.
Recently, too, but also when I first joined the group.
I came all the way from Hiroshima by myself.
I was quite anxious and lonely at times.
I was very happy to have you by my side.
I was so happy to have you by my side as if I had a big sister in Tokyo.
She took me to various restaurants.
She came to see me.
Yes.
For the first time, we went to a hamburger restaurant that wasn't part of a chain.
Yes, I ate a very delicious hamburger, and it left a deep impression on me.
I had a lot of impressions of eating a lot of food, so I put them all together and called it eating a lot of food.
And, after all, Ruru turned 23 years old last Tuesday, and I was asked to give my 23 year-old pledge.
I'm very excited because 23 is Omama's favorite number!
I'm already 23 years old!
I don't know where the "triple" is, but I think it will be a year of special happiness.
I'm sure you'll be very happy.
That's right. Now that that's assured, all we can do is to enjoy it to the fullest.
Please enjoy the year with all your heart.
We'll take questions for Mr. Oma after the VTR.
Hello! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11
Temptation. Love and Joy to the forecast.
Here, change it.
Take away handle Sleepless Love
Juice Juice News Single Tokyo Blab
Now on sale
I'm the one you don't have, I'm the one you don't have, I'm the one you come to when you sleep
You always know
So it's an ambiguous line
Juice Juice News Single Naimono Love
Now on sale
Kirakira no tomorrow kara Love wo cheering you on
Natsukaze Dancing Down
Juice Juice News Single Owako
Now on sale
Halo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask you a question.
Yes, I do.
I'll go now.
Next week on the 23rd, the photo book Strelitzia will be released.
What kind of information do you want from Uemura?
What's in the book?
Yes, sir.
It's a book filled with the things I want to share with you.
In connection with the news single "Love for Nothing
What is something that the members have recently had that you wanted?
A miso soup that Ichika Arisawa had.
What do you think of me and my love child?
Height?
Certainly.
What is your favorite Juice=Juice song?
I want to do this and that.
Yes, I do.
It's been about a year since we became the current 11 members.
What is the best word to describe Juice=Juice with 11 members?
Freedom
Thank you very much.
What is the one thing that the members have and want to have in connection with the "love what you don't have"?
Ichika's miso soup
I think it was instant miso soup in the dressing room.
Ichika was drinking it warmly and gave me a sip.
But it was so delicious that I couldn't ask her to give me a second sip.
I couldn't say that.
I thought I wanted it at that moment.
It's nice.
And your photo book "Strelitzia" is now on sale.
What kind of book is it?
The release date is in honor of 23 of my favorite 23.
It's really different from the previous three books.
Well...
I chose and applied the photos page by page.
I chose and applied the photos, the costumes, the locations.
I chose the costumes and the locations, and I was involved in all of it.
I really wanted to give you a book full of the me that I wanted to give you.
I think I've put everything into this book that I wanted to share with you.
Lulu... on the day of the shoot...
That's right, there was a shooting day in Tokyo.
I was just there as a staff member.
They used a hair dryer to clock my bangs.
And there were two makeup artists.
I had no experience like that.
I had never experienced anything like that before.
It was a lot of fun.
I was able to see a lot of different aspects of Mr. Kamimura.
I'm looking forward to seeing more photos of you in Kagoshima.
Haloste will continue after this.
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyabi!
Here we go, Hello Kitchen!
This time, we have a member here with us.
This is Homare Okamura from Morning Musume。
I don't usually cook, but I'll do my best today.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you today.
What would you like to cook this time?
Teriyaki Burger
Teriyaki burger.
Have you ever cooked anything before?
No, I don't usually cook. I just fry an egg and sausage for breakfast.
I think there might be some things that are a little difficult today.
If that's the case, the teacher will take care of it, so don't worry about it.
Let's work hard!
I'll do my best.
All right, let's see what we're going to do first.
We're going to make patties for the burgers.
It's better to put a little onion in the patties to make them juicier.
First of all, chop it.
Chop it up.
Yes, I'm going to chop it.
I don't usually do that.
I don't.
You said you don't cook.
How many times have you cooked?
Yes... in elementary school.
Like in elementary school?
Like a cooking class?
I have to show it.
Like, what you made?
Since then.
Not since then.
The only other thing I do is make curry with my mom.
But she's late, so she does everything.
I can't wait any longer.
What do you think?
Like this?
Yes, it's like this.
It's a shortcut, too.
Put it in a plastic bag.
I do this every time.
Microwave?
Yes, I do.
I've never done it before.
I've never done it.
I haven't seen you in a while, Mare.
You're tall.
Yes, she is.
It's been a while since we last met.
It's been a while.
How long?
Last year, right?
So not at all.
At that time and when you were wearing the boots in the costume.
I might have said you were tall.
I thought you were tall and slender even without them today.
I thought you looked slender even without them today.
Have you grown again?
I don't think so.
I don't think he's grown anymore, but he's tall.
You're the tallest among the members.
Yes, I'm the tallest so far.
You have good style, don't you?
One of the 17th term members, Tako Yumigami
She's still in middle school.
She's going to be a high school student next, so she's still growing.
In a little while...
Or maybe they'll do it to her.
How do you feel about that?
You don't like it?
I don't mind it.
I've never been overtaken since I joined.
I wonder if there will be people who will look up to me.
I don't know.
How long do you microwave this for?
I think 1 minute at 600W is enough.
It's crystal clear like this.
I think that's enough.
It's hot, so if you mix it in with the putty like this, it's hot.
It's hot.
It's warm!
It's going to burn, so I put it in the fridge or the freezer.
Now what do we do next?
Well, now it's time to do the best part.
We're going to make patties.
I'm going to make a patty, which is similar to the way a hamburger steak is made, so I'm going to start with an egg.
First of all, one egg for 300 grams of muscle is a bit much.
So, break it once and dissolve it.
And then cut it in half.
And then cut it in half like this.
Then add the egg at the end.
Okay.
Then, let's crack an egg.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
No problem at all.
She can't even crack an egg.
Shall I put some milk in the breadcrumbs?
Yes, 10 grams of breadcrumbs and 10 cc of milk.
And here's a little point.
Put the ground meat in a bowl and sprinkle salt on it.
I want to knead it without any other ingredients.
It's better to put it all together first.
How much salt do you put in?
You can add 1%, but I use a little less.
2 grams
It looks like slime.
Is this your first time?
I think I did ground meat a long time ago.
It's been a long time.
It's been a while.
Yes, sir.
When you get it together, you can use both hands. The hamburger has to stick to the joint.
If it's not sticky and slime-like, it will fall apart when you cook it, and the juices will run out through the holes.
And if you do it with just salt, it breaks down the proteins and makes it stickier and easier to form.
I'm sure you've been collecting all kinds of cute omelettes.
I like "Boo-Boo" in general, but right now I like the character of "Boo-Boo" a lot.
I love a character called "Punch Rabbit" and I'm working on it.
I'm shouting out to the character, and I've already found one.
There are a lot of new merchandise releases and crane games, so I often find out what week they're going to be released, or what week they're going to be released in the fourth week of the fourth week of the fourth week of the fourth week of the fourth week of the fourth week of the fourth week of the fourth month.
I'll definitely go with my mother when it's decided.
I'm going to go with her for the third time, too.
I'm going to let the air out this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way.
You've done this before, haven't you? You've done this before, haven't you?
Make the putty a little bigger. If you make it too big or too thick, it'll puff up.
If you make it too big or too thick, it will expand more than expected, so it's better to make it flat.
It will puff up like a hamburger steak. That's fine, but I think it will be a big problem.
If you want to put vegetables or something, this product is specific to hamburgers.
A little bigger. It's good.
It's not pretty. I think it'll work. It'll be good.
Now then, let's cut the vegetables.
It's better to have fresh vegetables in the burger.
We're going to be extravagant today.
You like meat, right, Mura?
That's right. I like meat.
I hear your Instagram is full of meat.
I'd love to see it.
What kind of meat do you like best?
Beef tendon.
I also love beef tongue.
I know what you mean.
You do it so well.
That's why I like it sliced.
It's a little bit thicker, but it takes a while to cook, so it's a lentil dish, too.
A little sprinkle of salt before you put it in the microwave, so the water comes out easier.
And then you start cutting into the lettuce right here, and then you take a little bit of each slice or two.
Then you cut into the lettuce from here, and you take a piece or two of lettuce, and you make it like this.
And then, since the core is a little bit hard, you can cut off a little bit of the core here and then put it in the burger.
So that's what it is.
Butter is the one you put on the buns.
Butter, I want to mix it with mustard.
I want to mix the butter with the mustard, but it's a little bit like pomade.
It's a little bit like pomade
I want to mix it with mustard if it's butter I want to mix it with mustard
Cream, like smooth cream
Cream, like smooth cream, but with or without this on the bun.
It depends on whether you put it on the bun or not.
Is it like that?
So that's all for this time.
That's all for now.
That's all for this time, please look forward to the next installment!
Bye bye!
Is it burnt?
It's so good, isn't it?
Delicious! Your eyes are shining!
This is Halo! Stay!" on June 14 at the Nippon Budokan.
Juice=Juice Concert Tour 2024 One Line Akari Uemura Graduation Special will be held at Nippon Budokan on June 14!
This time, I would like to ask Ms. Uemura some questions about her graduation.
And after a long time, Ann! This is Danbara, our reporter.
It's been a while.
For those of you who don't know me, I'm on the "Omake" channel.
I used to do this for about 3 or 4 years ago, and I've revived it for the first time in a long time.
It's been a while since I've revived it, so I'd like to thank you for your interest.
What are your frank feelings now that you have only one month left until your graduation?
I'm just looking forward to having all the fun I can.
Yes, that's right.
I guess...
I still cherish the live performances as I have in the past, but I've never really wanted to make memories, so my camera folder is overflowing at the moment.
Uemura-san herself doesn't seem to be expressing her graduation yet.
Not yet, not yet.
But the thing I felt the most was...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
When we were filming the music video, Kazuhiko was crying during the filming because it was a song from Mr. Tsugu, so it was a bit like a memorial.
I saw some of the members crying during the shooting, and I think that's when I felt it the most.
You have been a leader for the past two and a half years. What kind of leader do you think you are objectively?
Yes, I guess you can say that objectively.
Yes, as a person who stands for freedom.
I mean, I am a leader in the sense that each member has a leadership role, but I don't think I am bound to be a leader to that extent.
So I think we were equal leaders.
Yes, I have worked with the 3rd leader and the 1st and 2nd leaders.
I have the impression that the atmosphere of the group changes depending on the leader.
I feel that the current members are Uemura-san's children in many ways.
I think it is because of Mr. Uemura that the atmosphere of the group has become what it is today.
Rather than just saying, "Let's do it this way," he says, "You're doing it this way, so let's do it this way.
I think many of them are like that.
That's exactly right.
That's why they do things freely.
I have the impression that many of them are able to make their own choices, or rather, they are able to think and decide the direction they want to take.
I really like the atmosphere of Juice=Juice now.
I really like the atmosphere of Juice=Juice right now. Stage!
What do you feel about the current tour?
Yes!
There is a hyphen or a "pit" between the words "One Line".
This is to express our feelings as one, and also to express the connection with our history.
It also represents the connection with the history of Juhi+ and Juhi+.
I'd like to update it a little bit, and I'd like to make it a part of the Juhi+Halo! Concert Tour Project 4
I also want to set the axis of the project, and I also want to make the horizontal rows more beautiful.
So I want to make it beautiful no matter where you look at it from, which is the idea behind the tour title.
So I want to make this a live tour where you can naturally learn how to do that while being conscious of all these aspects.
We also want to make this a live tour where you can learn this naturally, and we really think about the connection with everyone.
I really want you to fully enjoy the feelings that we are able to deliver to you.
Also, I mentioned earlier that the one line of the graduation special is a hyphen.
I told you that only for the graduation special, it's an equal sign between the juices.
What's the truth behind that?
Great! You're a reporter in your own right!
It's also because it's a symbol that Juice Juice cherished.
And of course, it also means that we are on equal lines with each other.
But it also expresses the idea that we are truly connected.
You know, what I just said...
You know...
I was just saying that the part of us connected by the hyphen has become a complete body.
The equal has a lot of things in it.
I hope you all will feel free to explain it to me.
Lastly, I would like to ask you what the Juice Juice Hello Project means to you, Mr. Uemura.
I would like to ask you what the Hello Project means to you.
Great!
It's difficult, isn't it?
It is difficult, isn't it?
It's still difficult, isn't it?
If it weren't for the Hello Project, Juice Juice wouldn't be here today.
In a larger sense, I mean...
Although we are not related by blood, we are all genetically connected.
I feel that although we are not related by blood, we are all genetically connected.
I want people to inherit that while feeling the genetic connection.
Overseas tours are a great example of this.
This is one of the biggest examples.
I want to share this experience with my seniors.
I think it is important for us to carry out activities to pass on this experience to our juniors.
I don't want to bring this experience to the younger members of the group.
I think there are many things that have been passed down from generation to generation in that sense.
Thank you very much for your kind attention.
Please give a message to those who are coming to the graduation performance.
We would like to make June 14th a live where we can show our gratitude to all the people who have supported us since the formation of the group.
If you are not able to come, I would like to express my gratitude to all of you through this limited time.
I will also work hard for the activities of Juice=Juice so that I can show my appreciation to those of you who can't come to the live.
Thank you very much for watching.
Today, the trainees of Hello Project are going to perform solo.
Hello Project trainees will show you the results of their daily lessons in their solo performances.
This is a diagnostic test of their abilities.
It is not uncommon for today's test to be the beginning of their debut.
It is a very important event for the trainees.
And now, the next stage is the free song performance, which is all self-produced.
The next is the free song block, where all the performances, costumes, etc. are self-produced.
When the cold wind died down
I suddenly felt lonely
I felt a pain in my heart
Oh, notice me
I don't want to deceive
I don't want you to cheat me
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
Just do it
Someone's waiting for morning at the bottom of the night
I'll tell them
Dance baby dance baby dance baby dance baby
Fade up to the good word, I'll go around his words
Tell me what's weird No, I don't want to know
Ah Ah Ah Ah
Thinking in front of everyone
It's up to love to mess it up
Ideals always seem to hurt
I know, I know, I know
Sometimes I'm jealous
Kiss me again, sexy.
You're such a hard-ass
That's the beauty of it.
Sometimes I'm jealous
You're so bright again
Ah, you're so heavenly
Love like a rose
A bright red rose
When I lived alone in Tokyo
I felt the kindness of the umbrella in my heart
Because I was alone in Tokyo
I could fall in love with him.
I'm heartbroken.
Is it okay if I cry?
I glance up at the cherry blossoms
Melting into the beautiful night sky
We'll always be in love
We'll hold hands and make cute love
-end-
Forever Ah, the red free stadium
Swear to me you'll make it legendary
It's been almost a year
It's been almost a year since we met
I love you
When I don't see you for a while
I feel a little vulnerable.
You're good.
You're surprisingly carefree and you don't even notice me
Hey Hey, I've got a pretty face Hey Hey, I've got the best curry
Safe kill is this love journey
I'm ready for whatever end is in store
There's hardly any time to spare
I'm just desperately trying to hold on
It's definitely not you
me
ni
I don't have any, but...
I wonder if I'm allowed to be stupid
It's easy to do things here and there.
I'll be on the next bus.
I want to go home.
Please hold me, my instincts are a little strong.
Please hold me, please hold me, please hold me, please hold me, please hold me, please hold me, please hold me
Please understand me all I'm just a little bit selfish
Please understand everything You can never love me too much
You can never love me too much
Thank you very much.
Now we will announce the results of the judging.
First of all, I would like to start with the Jury's Special Awards.
The first one is the Makoto Award.
This is Soma Yume.
Congratulations!
Next is the Jury's Special Prize.
I would like to ask Ms. Maki Mitsuhashi to make an announcement.
The dance award goes to
Congratulations Sugihara!
Congratulations, Ms. Sugihara!
And now, for the Special Jury Prize, we have Ms. Ueno.
And for the singing award, congratulations to Mr. Hikaru Yoshida.
Congratulations, Mr. Yoshida.
Thank you very much.
And now, the last jury's special award.
The Inaba Manaka Ogata Risa Award.
Ms. Ogata, please make the announcement.
Okay, I'm going to announce it now.
The winner of the Risa Inaba Manaka Ogata Award is Itsuki Nishimura.
Congratulations!
Now finally, we only have one more award left to announce, which will be decided by the votes of our fans.
The Best Performance Award, which will be decided by the votes of the fans, remains to be announced!
Yes, Mr. Inaba will make the announcement and present the award!
Congratulations!
Congratulations to Mr. Inaba!
Ms. Inaba, please come on stage.
Hello Project Trainees Presentation 2024 Spring Open Proficiency Test
The winner of the Best Performance Award is...
Nina Hayashi.
Congratulations to Nina Hayashi.
Congratulations.
Now, Ms. Hayashi, please come to the middle.
Let's go to the middle.
Come on.
From Ms. Inaba
For the Best Performance of the Year Award.
The trophy.
Mr. Inaba will be presenting the trophy.
Congratulations.
Applause.
I've seen Mr. Kawashima winning the Best Performance Award here for a year now.
I thought that I wanted to be an anaf next year, too.
I'm very happy to know that my efforts have been conveyed to you all.
I'm very happy. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Please give a big round of applause again for Ms. Hayashi.
Please give a big round of applause for Ms. Hayashi.
This is such a wonderful event to shed such pure and beautiful tears.
I think it's because of your support that this event was made possible.
I would like to ask everyone to please continue to support the Hal Pro trainees.
Thank you very much.
Applause
This is Akari Uemura from Juice Juice and
Rambaralulu here with you on Haloste.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Juice Juice's new single Tokyo Bra
Naimono Love Aiko was released today!
Thank you very much!
This means that no one is really...
For me, this is the last single of Juice Juice.
It's a triple A May single that I've put a lot of thought into.
And the photo book "Lulu Lulu" by Lanbaralulu is now on sale!
I had the opportunity to shoot my first photo book in Yakushi.
Surrounded by the great nature
We were blessed with beautiful weather and relaxed during the shoot.
We wore a lot of beautiful outfits.
Please check them out!
And Akari Uemura's fourth photo book, Strevature
It will be on sale next week on the 23rd!
It will be on sale soon!
So I really put a lot of thought into it, from the costumes to the locations.
I'm really, really proud of it.
I think it's going to be a book that shows you how cute and how cool I am.
I think it's going to be a book that shows you that side of me.
And what can I say?
We also have a lot of adorable pictures of her with her big dog, a golden dog.
There are a lot of adorable things in this book.
Please check it out as well!
And on May 29th
Juice Juicetenth Anniversary Concert Tour 2023
Final Juice Story will be released!
Last year, Juice Juice spent one year as our 10th anniversary year.
The performance at Nippon Budokan, which will be the conclusion of the tour, will be made into a video work.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
Juice Juice Concert Tour 2024 One Line is now underway!
At the end of this year, we will be performing two shows in Fukuoka.
Please come and see us if you are in the area!
We look forward to seeing you there!
And on June 14th at the Nippon Budokan
Juice Juice Concert Tour 2024 One Line
Uemura Agari Graduation Special will be held!
This will be the last show of the spring tour and the last show for me, Uemura.
Please look forward to it!
Yes, sir!
And on July 15th
I will be performing at Juice Juice Lucky Fest!
It will be my first time to perform at this festival.
I am very much looking forward to it!
It will be held at the Hitachi Seaside National Park.
Please check it out!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Agari Kamimura of Juice Juice and
and Dombara Ruru from Juice Juice
and Ruru Dombara of Juice Juice!
Good bye.